Ah, looks like new pages are appearing.
I wonder what'll happen next.
The brothers delayed their trip
and took a bus four hours later,
so they managed to avoid getting
into an accident. Yippee!
What adventures awaited them now?
Once in Aswan, they made their discovery.
Oh, there they are, the five
bad guys, cried the brothers.
But the brothers wondered, what
could they be talking about?
The bad guys seemed so worried.
Mm-hmm.
I think that's them.
Little did they know,
they had drunk poison tea.
Look.
Brother, check it out.
Earth's a big bro.
Huh?
So I just have to poison them.
Listen, little bro,
you and I are practically invincible together
between your clairvoyant comic, Stan,
and my face, Stan's
transformative ability!
No one can get in our way!
Those guys are as good as dead!
We possess the cards known
as Death, the god of writing,
and K 'nom, the god of creation!
and together we are the
bestest brothers ever!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Hell, Hell, Hell!
Hell, Hell, Hell, Hell!
It's here in this cafe,
right at that table.
That's where those guys
will drink their poison tea.
Yeah,
my Stan Thoth, the god of writing,
has never been wrong about anything
when it comes to predictions.
Well, are they going to pull through?
Luckily,
Avdol's major arteries weren't damaged,
so he'll probably be released by tomorrow.
But Kakyoin, on the other hand, has
serious injuries that need to be treated.
There's a chance he could go blind.
That's a raw deal.
I hate to say it, but if his
condition doesn't improve soon,
we might have to leave him behind.
Uh-huh.
Hey, since there are so many cafes nearby,
how about we get ourselves a drink?
That's a great idea.
Which one did you have in mind?
There you have it.
The cigarette has spoken.
Hello there.
Tell me, sirs, how may I be of service?
Well, tea sounds good
right about now. Same.
Right, so three teas.
Be back in a jiffy.
Actually, scratch that order
if you would. Huh? Hear me out.
We're in enemy territory here.
This is Dio's dominion, and since we
don't know when enemies will attack,
we have to be cautious.
If we let our guard down, even for
a second, someone could poison us.
From this point on, we're only
drinking from bottles and cans.
Come on.
Are you serious? Completely.
Hey there, you can forget the
tea and bring us colas instead.
Huh?
Cola!
That's right.
Something wrong?
not at all okay three colas coming
up hmm I'll just go and grab
them oh by the way if you don't
mind we'll open them ourselves
and to make sure we're not falling
victim to any funny business
give us the third fourth and
fifth ones from the far right
side now they want unopened
colas how am I supposed to put
poison in those was the prediction
wrong no that can't be it my
brother's comic is always right
damn it I've got to get it
together I just have to believe
if I don't have absolute faith in
little bro we won't stand a
chance yes my predictions are
foolproof brother you in the apron
is this warm cola your idea of
a cold drink you must assume
I'm a real half-wit or something
to think I'd pay for this excuse
of a beverage wait what the
coal is really not cold sorry
about the hassle the fridge is
down so hey don't you think you're
being a little paranoid let's
say for the sake of argument
that guy was our enemy and he was
trying has damned us to slip a
little poison into our drinks.
How would he have known to
come to this exact cafe?
I mean, the city's not lacking
in places to get a drink.
And I chose this one on a whim.
I'd understand if this were the only
cafe, but there are tons of them.
My point is, we can't be
too careful around here.
Well, if you're that worried,
let's go somewhere else then.
Maybe the place across the street.
Hmm.
What do I do?
My cafe is on fire! Ow! No!
Some fool left a burning cigarette
in the road and it ignited the trash!
Oh, boy.
You know what?
I think we'll take those teas after all.
Yes, we did it.
Zootalor.
What kind of jerk would toss a
lit cigarette near the trash?
Really, the nerve of some people.
Finally, they're drinking it.
Drink it. Drink it.
Drink it till it's gone.
They drank it!
A dog just took my cake!
Who the hell brought a mangy
mutt to a freakin' cafe?
Iggy!
Will somebody please get
this dog out of here?
Dammit, Iggy!
Get back here, you fleabag!
Damn it!
They were just about
to swallow the poison!
Dumb mutt.
So what the hell's
supposed to happen next?
Well, thing is, the page
hasn't appeared yet.
Also, while off, it wasn't
entirely wrong. Be patient.
Thoth only has the ability to see
the near future, so patience is key.
Next time, then.
When the next premonition is revealed,
we'll use it to destroy them.
This is what we were meant to do.
Together, we're the bestest
brothers ever, baby!
We failed to kill them
because of that darn dog!
We were so close, Fume, the brothers.
The brothers were beside themselves
with anger because their plan failed.
But the brothers didn't give up,
and soon they decided to follow
the three guys and their dog.
While following them, they met a
man who had a very annoying face,
the kind of face that was
just begging to be hit.
In fact, it was the kind
of face the brothers hated.
I must have hated that
face in a past life.
And a face like that
deserves a knuckle sandwich.
Even though he was a perfectly nice
man, Big Bro punched him anyway.
Thus, the man with the bad face ran away.
But fortunately for them, he
dropped a wallet full of money.
Yay, we're rich!
Whoopee, cried Mondatta.
What a dumbass.
Yeah, thanks to that
smarmy-faced fool, we're rich.
Hey, brother, check it out.
The new page is coming.
The brothers continued their pursuit.
The bad guys got in their car and hurried
over to the hospital to
check on their friends,
Abdal and Kakuin.
But they had no idea
Zenyatta had made a bomb,
placed it in an orange,
and planted it in the car.
Jotaro was blown into a million pieces.
His head was split in two.
and his blood was splattered everywhere!
L-l-look how clearly the
pictures in the comet came in!
I see!
It's true that my stan thoth
can only see the near future,
and most would see that
as a disadvantage, but
once the prediction has been printed,
it can't be changed no
matter what anybody does.
Not ever.
We're gonna blow Jotaro to smithereens.
The bomb will detonate three seconds
after he sticks his finger in to peel it.
It's destiny!
This is the end.
There's no way out.
Who the hell is in our car?
Do you recognize this bozo? What?
Isn't it Jotaro? No.
Jotaro said he was going
straight to the hospital.
Be careful.
Damn it.
Don't let him get away.
You've got to be kidding.
It's Joestar and Polnareff.
Whoever you are, come out this instant.
What he said, out of the car.
Quit your stolen and get
out of there already.
Make it snappy!
Hey, hey, what's the matter with you two?
It was me, couldn't you tell?
Oh, so it was you, Jotaro.
My stand, Kanam, gives me
the power of transformation.
I can alter my height, weight,
and scent however I see fit.
I even used my hair to recreate this hat.
Wait, I don't get it.
Last I heard, you said you were going
to head straight for the hospital.
Huh? I did.
Ah, the hospital.
I forgot something, so I
decided to come and get it.
Oh, that's right.
I left my wallet in the car. Good grief.
Jotaro, where's your school uniform?
Uniform?
What's he talking about?
What school uniform?
Nothing personal, friend, but that's
not really a good look on you.
Ah, my outfit.
I mean uniform.
Well, it's actually at the dry cleaners.
I took it in for a wash, but then
I realized I didn't have any money.
Yeah, that'll convince them.
I'm in the clear.
That's so. All right, then.
You can go ahead and hop in the car.
Time to go.
Oh, no! Not the car!
Then that would mean...
No, it can't be.
If I get into the car with this face,
that means the real Jotaro won't
be the one getting blown up.
Instead, it'll be me!
Shit.
You know, it's a beautiful day out, so
I think I'll go ahead and walk a lot.
We don't have time to wait
for you to walk there, Jotaro.
Things will go a lot faster if you just
get in the car and ride over with us.
Brother, you have to get out of there now!
Crap, this is bad.
I've got to undo my Jotaro
disguise before it's too late.
If I don't, I'll be the
one who gets blown to bits.
Instead, that's it.
I just need to throw it away.
I'll covertly get rid of this one
and put another one in the car
later so it can blow up the real
Jotaro thereby saving my ass.
I did it.
What a relief.
I'm safe.
Hey, what do you know? It's Iggy.
He's chasing our car.
He's got an orange in. his mouth.
Did you steal that, Eggie?
It'll make a nice gift
for Kakyo-ing an Avdol.
What? Yow!
Come again?
Everything okay?
Never thought I'd hear you
say something like that.
Oh, really? That's weird. Yow?
You know, yow.
Actually, I was pointing
out that there's a cow
over there. A cow?
Man, you sure are acting
pretty peculiar today, Jotaro.
You're usually a lot
cooler I hate to say this
but I've got to wonder
you're not really a fake
are you Jotaro
good
grief
Balmer F what the hell
are you even talking
about man by By the way,
are we at the hospital yet?
Hey, Jotaro, I'm super bored, so how
about you show me that trick again?
A trick?
Which one is that?
What's he talking about?
The one you taught me a while back?
You know, this one here.
Hey, you've gotten a bit
better at that, Polnareff.
Oh, that's the trick
you were talking about.
Thank goodness.
I know how to do that one.
It's risky, but I can pull it off.
Why didn't you say so from the beginning?
That's an easy one. All right.
In that case, do the one
with five cigarettes then.
Five cigarettes?
Hurry it up already, would you?
I want to see the trick again.
Why is this happening to me?
Damn that Jotaro and damn
his stupid party tricks.
But if I don't at least try to do it,
they'll really think something is up,
and they're already becoming more
suspicious of me by the minute!
And Polnareff,
loathsome idiot that he is, is seconds
away from setting off the bomb!
Alright, fine, dammit!
I'll do it!
Have it your way, five cigarettes.
That's the way, now come on, do the trick!
Alright, it's now or never.
I'm gonna do it, I'm gonna
do the trick, dammit!
Here goes nothing.
I did it, hot damn, I did it!
There! Did you see that? I did it!
A man can do anything when
his life is on the line.
Here.
Last time you did this super
cool move where you drank
a bottle of juice without
putting the cigarettes out.
Come on, drink up.
Oh, you blew it!
Jotaro, are you alright?
Oh my god!
Brother!
Brother, please! Blue bro!
Make that prediction go away right now!
Tear up that page!
Sorry, big bro, but the
prediction can't be changed.
Hurry and go back to your regular self!
If you can undo the disguise, the
real Jotaro will get blown up instead.
I believe in you, brother.
Jotaro, I know we've said this already,
but you're acting really weird today.
It's nothing.
I just feel a little
under the weather is all.
Crap, this couldn't get any worse.
I know their type.
Since I've put them on guard,
they're going to interrogate
me and realize I'm an imposter.
If they figure me out, they'll kill me.
And if I don't undo my disguise, I'll
blow up just like the prophecy said.
That's it!
I'll just pretend I'm sick and make them
let me out of the car to relieve myself.
Brilliant!
Jotaro, I couldn't help but notice
the way you're clasping your hands.
Aha!
Are you aware you've got your
left thumb on top of the others?
Well, are you?
Damn it, I wasn't prepared for this.
Does Jotaro have a weird
tick that causes him
to clasp his hands with
his right thumb on top?
Who even notices something like that?
What am I gonna do?
That just proves beyond a shadow of a
doubt that you are a woman in a past life.
And since unlike you, I always
put my right thumb on top,
it proves that I was
a man in my past life.
Wow, now how about that?
I always put my left thumb on top as well.
Sorry, Mr.
Joestar, but that proves you
too were a woman in a past life.
Says you, how does it prove anything?
How do thumbs factor into reincarnation?
That's so stupid!
Now I really do feel sick.
Beast-rabbit lunatics are
driving me up the wall!
Alright, I'll tell them
I've got a stomachache.
Jotaro, what do you say we find out which
one of us can eat an orange the fastest?
Say what?
Hey, maybe you...
Stop it!
Don't do that, you idiot!
Whoa there!
What the hell are you doing, Jotaro?
What's going on with you today, Jotaro?
Oh, it's nothing, guys.
But this isn't like you at all.
I just don't think it's good for
you to eat that particular orange.
What's the problem with it?
Well, it's obvious, isn't it?
Who knows where the heck
Iggy found that thing?
For all we know, he could
have dug it out of the gutter.
You should eat a different one.
Thanks for caring, but it doesn't look
bruised or dirty, so I think I'll be fine.
I'll eat this one, and
you can have one of those.
I can't wait to see the look
on your face when I win.
Ow! The pain!
Huh? Please.
Hey, what's wrong?
Stop the car.
I have to go to the bathroom.
Come on, stop the car. Hurry!
Does your stomach really hurt that bad?
I can't hold it anymore!
Let me out! Let me out!
I'll go behind that rock!
The hospitals right there just hang
on no no going ahead without me.
I'll catch up once I'm done
Not so fast Jotaro
Take this, it's... Yes!
I did it!
I can't believe I did it!
I actually managed to get out
of that metal death trap alive!
I'll go behind that rock
and undo my disguise!
He brought up a good point.
Who knows where Iggy found this orange?
For all we know, it could
have been lying in the gutter.
Do you want to eat it?
Nah, you can toss it.
Success!
Now I can use K 'num's powers
to transform back to normal!
After that, they'll get
what's coming to them!
And the Dinyana Maiden
brothers will have won again!
We win!
Are you kidding me?!
Huh?
Did you hear that sound?
Just forget it.
It was probably construction.
Big bro, are you okay?
Speak to me.
Hey, little bro.
I think we lost this
battle. Bad. Really bad.
No, big brother.
No. No way.
Those wannabes haven't beaten
me and my Stan Thoth yet.
I'll destroy them all, brother.
By myself if I have to.
No, don't.
Don't do this brother.
These guys aren't some rookies
you can push around You'll die.
I've already decided and
I can beat them on my own.
I know I can
You were always so shy you've
really grown up little bro
I'm gonna kill them all.
What does the book of thoughts say next?
This is them, all right.
They're the ones who punched me and
purloined my wallet while they were at it.
All right, then.
Beat them to a bloody pulp, and I'll
make sure you're rewarded handsomely.
It's him again!
I'm scared, brother.
This doesn't look good for us.
Despite his intense yet
short-lived burst of bravery,
Mondatta would have to wait a
while to avenge his brother.
But try not to lose heart, Mondatta.
Life is full of wonderful
ups and terrible downs.
Huh?
Well, if it isn't Jotaro. Hm?
Hey, what took so long?
Forget that.
How'd you take a dump behind
that rock so fast? Huh?
I can't believe you got here before us.
You even found time to
go to the dry cleaners.
What the hell are you two talking about?
Hey, it's an ambulance.
Someone must be heard.
Aw, man, that's unfortunate.
Hmm?
Oranges, huh?
I was just getting thirsty.
Think I'll take one.
Huh?
What's this?
That man's clothes.
You recognize him?
Nope, can't say that I do.
Right, let's go find out how
Avdol and Kakyoin are doing.
Huh.
And so the brothers eventually
gave up on their mission.
The battle was over, and after
all the chaos and the pain,
Jojaro and the others were
none the wiser. Ba-dum!
I believe!
Oingo! Oingo! Brothers!
I can move on to Oingo!
It's a good thing. It's a good thing.
It's a good thing.
All of them are all up.
It's so good, right?
You've been a good thing.
The evidence of the evidence
is that you can't be done.
The evidence of the
truth is that you can't.
I'm so excited!
You're so excited!
That's right, right?
Boeing-A-Boeing-A Brothers!
I believe it!
You don't have to hit me!
I'm so excited!
I think I'll hack you to
pieces while I'm on a roll.
You shall wield me, and you shall kill.
Let's see if your Anubis stand
is all it's cracked up to be.